# [photo]

# Demid Moshkovich

python developer

## About me

I'm a developer from Minsk, Belarus. Mostly, I'm self-taught, so now I have experience in many IT areas and I can adapt to almost any requirements

With several years of experience, ranging from web development to algorithmics, I took part in some conferences and olympiads and worked as a freelancer

## Soft skills

- communication
- collaboration
- passion for education
- leadership

## Hard skills

PYTHON ————————————————————————————————————	90% 
DJANGO	70%
<u>C++</u>	60%
WEB	70%
SQL	50%

## Get in touch

MAIL: strannik.kraya575721@gmail.com

TELEGRAM: @irongun

HABR FREELANCE: @IronGun

GITHUB: @IronGunYT

MY WEBSITE: \*coming soon\*

## Resume

## Experience

#### ○ 苗 2020-2023

## PET PROJECTS

I made several pet projects, such as my portfolio website, a web game, several web utilities and two telegram bots. You can find sources on my GitHub

#### **苗** 2022-2023

## **FREELANCE**

I worked as a freelancer and did various projects, e.g. web scrapers and websites with complex server architecture

#### 

## **TEACHING**

I teach students the basics of programming languages and algorithms

#### 

## CONFERENCES AND OLYMPIADS

In school, I took part in some competitions. For example, I took part in ICYS-2022(International Conference) with my team. We presented an app based on a neural network for finding the best placement of cameras in a room

## Education

#### 〇 苗 2022-now

### BSU

I study at BSU, FAMCS, "Applied Computer Science"

#### 苗 2021-2021

### MENTORING - VK TESTERS

I've completed VK testers manual QA educational course

## Skills & more information

My English level is about B2. I worked with:

- Python + Django
- Web(html+css+js)
- Scraping(bs4, selenium)
- C++
- and much more

You can also see my projects and full list of skills on my website and <u>GitHub</u>